const ExpertSystemsQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What is an Expert System?",
        options: ["Emulates human expert","Plays video games",  "Social network"],
        correct_option: "Emulates human expert"
    },
    {
        question: "Why are Expert Systems used?",
        options: ["Communicate with aliens", "Play music", "Solve complex problems"],
        correct_option: "Solve complex problems"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Knowledge Representation?",
        options: ["Art technique", "Store and organize info", "Build houses"],
        correct_option: "Store and organize info"
    },
    {
        question: "What is an Inference Engine?",
        options: ["Starts fires", "Car engine", "Processes knowledge"],
        correct_option: "Processes knowledge"
    },
    {
        question: "What is a Rule-Based System?",
        options: ["Food recipe", "Uses set of rules", "Play sports"],
        correct_option: "Uses set of rules"
    },
    {
        question: "Purpose of Expert System Shell?",
        options: ["Protects system", "Framework for building", "Protective covering"],
        correct_option: "Framework for building"
    },
    {
        question: "Role of Knowledge Engineer?",
        options: ["Repairs cars", "Organizes expert knowledge", "Designs clothes"],
        correct_option: "Organizes expert knowledge"
    },
    {
        question: "Difference from Conventional Programs?",
        options: ["No difference", "Incorporates human-like reasoning", "Faster than humans"],
        correct_option: "Incorporates human-like reasoning"
    },
    {
        question: "Limitation of Expert Systems?",
        options: [ "Solve problems within domain", "Faster than humans","Can solve any problem",],
        correct_option: "Solve problems within domain"
    },
    {
        question: "Example of Expert System Application?",
        options: ["Cook food","Play musical instruments",  "Diagnosing medical conditions"],
        correct_option: "Diagnosing medical conditions"
    }
];

export default ExpertSystemsQuestions;
